

# Jaka Potokar

**Business Informatics Student** 

💌 jaka.potokar50@gmail.com 🤳 +386 31 856 928 🛭 🝳 Vavpotičeva ulica 15, 1241 Kamnik

### **Profile**

Hello, my name is Jaka. I would describe myself as a kind and positive person. My virtues are that I am very organized, very punctual, precise, and always like to solve the problems I face. I am always ready to gain new experience and knowledge in new fields. Friends and co-workers would describe me as independent, self- initiated and team oriented.

### **Education**

#### MASTERS IN BUSINESS INFORMATICS

2023 - Present

University of Economics and Business Ljubljana, Ljubljana Business informatics program in english language in international class.

#### **BACHELORS IN INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS**

2020 - 2023

University of Economics and Business Ljubljana, Ljubljana International business program in english language in international class.

#### AUDENCIA BUSINESS SCHOOL NANTES -**ERASMUS +**

Sep 2022 - Dec 2022

Audencia Business School Nantes, Nantes

Erasmus+ exchange for one semester in Audencia Business School.

# **Employment**

#### DRUŠTVO AED - TEAM LEADER

Jan 2023 - Jan 2024

Društvo AED, Ljubljana

Leading a team of 20-30 promoters. I was in charge of filling and creating schedules, conducting meetings, recruiting, finding new locations, and helping in managing the current ones.

#### DRUŠTVO AED - PROMOTER

2022 - 2023

Društvo AED, Ljubljana

I had to convince customers of shopping centres to sign a paper that allows them to transfer 1% of income tax to our association.

# EMMA D.O.O. - ASSISTANCE IN THE SALES **DEPARTMENT - TELEPHONE AND FIELD SALES**

2020 - 2021

Emma D.O.O., Lesce

Assistance in telephone and field sales of products Vestina. And also all around help in sales department.

#### Personal details

Date of birth August 10, 2001

Driver's license **B** category

Gender

Male

Website jakapotokar.xyz

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/jaka-potokar-14452627b

Github

github.com/BChainbuddy

### Skills

Javascript

Python

Html, css

React

Nextis, Tailwindcss

Solidity

Hardhat

Node

Expressis

# EMMA D.O.O. – ASSISTANCE IN THE MARKETING DEPARTMENT – DIGITAL MARKETING

Emma D.O.O., Lesce

Editing and assistance in preparing content for facebook page vestina.eu, assistance in setting up an online store.

#### EMMA D.O.O. - WORK IN PRODUCTION

2016 - 2020

2020 - 2021

Emma D.O.O., Lesce

Assembling ecological electronic and solar candles of the Vestina brand and arranging a warehouse in company.

# Extracurricular activities

### **BNB Hackaton Dorahacks**

Feb 2024 - Mar 2024

Dorahacks

We created an application WeaveSwap that offers Decentralized exchange and Lending protocol to its users. I was responsible for architecting and creating the smart contracts for our product. Throughout this project, I gained valuable insights into the dynamics of effective teamwork and the importance of leveraging individual strengths to achieve a unified and efficient workflow.

Link to the build: https://dorahacks.io/buidl/10313

# AMCHAM SLOVENIA – FIRST MENTOR PROGRAM

2019 - 2020

Amcham Slovenia, Ljubljana

Mentored by Tina Zafred on the topic: switching between the education system and the career path.

# MOJEFINANCE - SUMMER FINANCIAL SCHOOL

2019 - 2019

Moje Finance, Ljubljana

Financial school which taught me a lot about personal finances, stock market, debt and other financial instruments.

# Certificates

# Full Stack Development Career Path, Codecademy

Present

(In Progress, 66% Completed). Specialized in front-end development with comprehensive knowledge in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React. Currently expanding skills in backend development and database management.

# The Complete SQL Bootcamp: Go from Zero to Hero

Oct 2023

A course from Udemy that introduced me to Postgresql and taught me everything I need to know to work with it.

## Learn Blockchain, Solidity, and Full Stack Web3 Development with JavaScript

May 2023

FreeCodeCamp (Self-Directed Study, 32 Hours). Focused on developing smart contracts using Solidity, integrating smart contracts with web applications, and understanding the

Postgresql

# Languages

Slovenian

English

German

Croatian

#### **Hobbies**

- Sports and Gym
- Travelling
- Cooking
- Education in the field of economics
- Education in the field of personal growth
- Education in the field of technology

fundamentals of blockchain technology.

# Algorithmic Trading & Technical Analysis

Apr 2021

Moralis academy course that introduced me to development of trading bots with javascript and development of trading strategies in pinescript on Tradingview.

# Javascript Programming for Blockchain Developers

Mar 2021

Moralis academy course that introduced me to javascript.